<resources>
    <string name="app_name">newsApp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="srinagar_kashmir_state_investigation_agency_has_announced_a_cash_reward_of_rs_10_lakh_for_anyone_providing_information_on_the_killers_of_senior_j_and_k_high_court_advocate_babar_qadri_who_was_gunned_down_by_terrorists_at_his_srinagar_residence_on_september_24_2020_the_informer_s_identity_would_be_kept_confidential_the_agency_has_assured_those_having_any_information_can_contact_the_sia_on_the_number_9103998467_call_whatsapp_signal_telegram_cash_reward_of_rs_10_00_000_is_announced_for_those_providing_information_leading_to_the_arrest_of_the_persons_involved_in_the_killing_of_senior_advocate_of_j_and_k_high_court_late_babar_qadri_of_zahidpora_hawal_srinagar_read_a_notice_issued_by_the_chief_investigation_officer_sit_sia_kashmir_digital_transformation_is_no_longer_a_luxury_it_has_become_a_necessity_for_companies_to_remain_competitive_and_relevant_in_their_respective_industries_india_s_spending_on_digital_transformation_is_likely_to_reach_86_billion_by_2026_according_to_the_international_data_corporation_idc_while_companies_are_adopting_they_still_have_a_long_way_to_go_this_is_because_many_companies_are_still_grappling_with_traditional_way_of_engaging_customers_managing_workflows_and_utilising_information_some_of_the_challenges_they_encounter_are_as_follows_1_digital_transformation_scattered_non_actionable_data_data_serves_as_the_vital_essence_of_any_business_as_companies_amass_vast_amounts_of_customer_data_however_this_data_often_remains_segregated_lacking_communication_between_different_sources_alternatively_the_data_may_exist_in_its_raw_form_harbouring_countless_valuable_yet_untapped_insights_that_have_the_potential_to_propel_businesses_forward_consequently_this_data_is_rendered_non_actionable_and_fails_to_be_optimised_for_effective_decision_making_weak_resource_management_and_collaboration_companies_labour_under_hundreds_of_applications_this_results_in_an_overload_of_vendors_and_a_sea_of_different_software_and_databases_it_can_lead_to_work_duplication_and_lower_collaboration_an_inability_to_keep_pace_with_customers_today_s_customers_have_significantly_changed_they_want_brands_to_intuitively_understand_their_needs_serve_them_effectively_on_mobile_web_and_social_media_and_move_at_their_pace_instead_of_the_other_way_around_brands_that_don_t_use_digital_technology_fail_to_understand_and_seamlessly_serve_their_customer_s_lag_currently_only_17_of_indian_businesses_deliver_exceptional_customer_services_though_79_say_improved_customer_experience_is_a_way_to_drive_revenue_2_slow_to_respond_to_change_the_lack_of_digital_transformation_can_make_it_harder_for_companies_to_gather_the_right_data_at_the_right_time_and_execute_the_right_intervention_that_in_turn_affects_their_speed_to_market_lower_value_creation_without_the_right_technologies_working_in_tandem_the_workflow_can_be_cumbersome_people_don_t_have_access_to_the_same_data_and_many_professionals_end_up_investing_significant_time_in_non_critical_tasks_that_s_why_it_s_crucial_for_senior_leaders_and_function_heads_to_rethink_digital_in_their_business_model_to_improve_productivity_customer_experience_and_profitability_ey_s_ceo_survey_2022_reported_that_50_of_respondents_expected_to_improve_profits_with_digital_and_technological_interventions">SRINAGAR: Kashmir State Investigation Agency ( ) has announced a cash reward of Rs 10 lakh for anyone providing information on the killers of senior J and K High Court advocate Babar Qadri, who was gunned down by terrorists at his Srinagar residence on September 24, 2020. The informer’s identity would be kept confidential, the agency has assured. Those having any information can contact the SIA on the number: 9103998467 (call/WhatsApp/Signal/Telegram). “Cash reward of Rs 10,00,000 is announced for those providing information leading to the arrest of the persons involved in the killing of senior advocate of J and K High Court, Late Babar Qadri, of Zahidpora, Hawal, Srinagar,” read a notice issued by the chief investigation officer SIT, SIA Kashmir.Digital transformation is no longer a luxury. It has become a necessity for companies to remain competitive and relevant in their respective industries. India’s spending on digital transformation is likely to reach $86 billion by 2026, according to the International Data Corporation (IDC) . While companies are adopting , they still have a long way to go. This is because many companies are still grappling with traditional way of engaging customers, managing workflows, and utilising information. Some of the challenges they encounter are as follows: 1 digital transformation Scattered, non-actionable data: Data serves as the vital essence of any business, as companies amass vast amounts of customer data. However, this data often remains segregated, lacking communication between different sources. Alternatively, the data may exist in its raw form, harbouring countless valuable yet untapped insights that have the potential to propel businesses forward. Consequently, this data is rendered non-actionable and fails to be optimised for effective decision-making. Weak resource management and collaboration: Companies labour under hundreds of applications. This results in an overload of vendors and a sea of different software and databases. It can lead to work duplication and lower collaboration. An inability to keep pace with customers: Today’s customers have significantly changed. They want brands to intuitively understand their needs, serve them effectively on mobile, web, and social media, and move at their pace instead of the other way around. Brands that don’t use digital technology fail to understand and seamlessly serve their customer’s lag. Currently, only 17% of Indian businesses deliver ‘exceptional’ customer services, though 79% say improved customer experience is a way to drive revenue . 2 Slow to respond to change: The lack of digital transformation can make it harder for companies to gather the right data at the right time and execute the right intervention. That, in turn, affects their speed-to-market. Lower value creation: Without the right technologies working in tandem, the workflow can be cumbersome, people don’t have access to the same data, and many professionals end up investing significant time in non-critical tasks. That’s why it’s crucial for senior leaders and function heads to rethink digital in their business model to improve productivity, customer experience, and profitability. EY’s CEO survey 2022 reported that 50% of respondents expected to improve profits with digital and technological interventions .</string>
</resources>